mojeh.com 2014-11-30

# MOJEH MAGAZINE, PRIVACY POLICY

MOJEH is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its on-line visitors, the following policy explains how MOJEH may use any information which you submit via this website.

**Requests for Personal Information**  
Some areas in MOJEH website may ask you for some personal information that will help us to follow up with you, enhance your visit to the site and may be used to support your customer relationship with MOJEH. Such information that requires your personal details are inquires about the followings:

• General Inquiries  
• Media Inquiries  
• Careers Inquiries  
• Information about a product or service

Inquiry fields may ask you about: your name, e-mail address, phone number, location, gender and type of business, in addition to other information that is needed to subscribe you to services or offers provided by MOJEH.

**Use of Personal Information**  
MOJEH, or its authorized agents, may use the details you provide for the following marketing purposes:  
• To enhance the service offered on the site and other MOJEH services.  
• To inform you of products/ services that you might find useful.  
• To respond directly to requests and queries that you may submit on the Contact Us page of MOJEH.com  
• To inform you about product upgrades, new product?services from MOJEH.

**Disclosure of Information**

MOJEH does not trade, rent, sell, any personal information gathered at our website.

**General**  
When there is no longer a requirement to store your personal information, MOJEH will delete the information from its systems. MOJEH reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without a notification.  
  
---|---|---
